Guide to the Arthur Kornberg Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Class Materials, 1953-1968; Series 5
  - Biochemistry 101-102 (examinations and review questions), 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Biochemistry 101-102, 1963-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Biochemistry 103, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biochemistry 103, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General chemistry workshop, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Biology 10-113, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Stanford Administrative and Departmental Records, 1961-1986; Series 6
  - Industrial Affiliates Program (Bio Chemistry Dept.), 1980-84 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary Scientific Symposia, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Roof Project: expansion of biochemistry building, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1961-62 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Budget Cuts, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Biochemistry dept. minutes, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  - Biochemistry dept. records (faculty minutes), 1971-1983 (Box 5)
  - Biochemistry dept. records (faculty minutes), 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Binder re Department Responsibilities, 1969-71 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee: minutes, agenda, reports, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Student unrest, 1968-69 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Student unrest, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford administrative files, 1968-71 (Box 1, Folder 13-20)
- Personal and Miscellaneous Papers, 1947-1979; Series 7
  - Newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5-11)
  - Newspaper clippings, publicity, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, 1947-52 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Personal, 1947-52 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 33, Folder 1-7)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971 and undated; Series 8
  - Slides: illustrations for lectures (Box 34-35)
  - Kornberg, Arthur: Membrane structure, 1971 Feb 22; 36.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 36)
  - Roseman, T.J.: Membrane function in permeation, 23-Feb-71; 36.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 36)
  - Kornberg, Arthur: Cell envelopes, Feb 24-26, 1971; 36.3-36.5; 3 audiocassette(s) (Box 36)
  - Bloch: Steroid structure and synthesis, 1971 Mar 2-3; 36.6-36.7; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 36)
  - Kornberg, Arthur: Opening address, Cold Spring Harbor, 1978; 36.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 36)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-108
  Partially restricted.
  - Others' work: Abir-Am-Cori (Box 1)
  - Others' work: Cozzarelli-Heppel (Box 2)
  - Others' work: Herschlag-Klenow (Box 3)
  - Others' work: Kline-Loeb (Box 4)
  - Others' work: Lohman-Okinawa (Box 5)
  - Others' work: Orgel-Thackray (Box 6)
  - Others' work: Thomas-Zuckerman (Box 7)
  - Poly P-files related to (Box 8)
  - Acmetobacter [Acinetobacter?]-other organisms (Box 8)
  - Poly P-files (Box 9)
  - Pavlov-XLL (Box 9)
  - Seminars, 1983-1988 (Box 9)
  - Seminars, 1989-1996 Jan. (Box 10)
  - Seminars, 1996 July-1999 Dec. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Germ Stories, 2007 (Box 11)
  - DNAX: Staffing-Eugenics, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Grant files (?) 007581 Revision, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Wednesday club (Box 13)
  - Reviews (Box 13)
  - Patent-Liposome (Box 13)
  - Clinician lecture (Box 14)
  - Course files (including some slides)-Biochem 202 May 1980 (Box 14)
  - General Files-Spyros-A; department files; course (Box 14)
  - Alphabetical through Ishige 2003 (Box 14)
  - Alphabetical: Kuroda-Z (Box 15)
  - Science & Society-Hargittai (Box 15)
  - DNAX 93-Schening-Plough (Box 15)
  - Alpha sequence: Affymetrix-Zyomyx (Box 16)
  - Presentations Jan. 2002-Jan. 2005 (Box 17)
  - Dean Search File 1964 [CONFIDENTIAL] (Box 17)
  - JBC MSS 1957-58 (Box 17)
  - Jardetsky appointment [CONFIDENTIAL] (Box 17)
  - Slides/illustrations-Gene A Rep (Box 17)
  - Presentations Jan. 2000-2001 (Box 18)
  - Nucleotic lecture (Box 18)
  - [box not full] (Box 18)
  - Department 1991 [folder with minutes, memos, financial statements, etc.] (Box 19)
  - Department 1992 [folder with minutes, memos, financial statements, etc.] (Box 19)
  - Binder: book reviews of Kornberg's Golden Helix (Box 19)
  - Bound volume: Collected reprints 1941-1954 (Box 19)
  - Bound volume: Reprints 1953-57 Dept. of Microbiology Washington University [Kornberg and other authors] (Box 19)
  - Bound volume: Reprints 1958-59 Dept. of Microbiology Washington University & 1959-60 Stanford University [Kornberg and other authors] (Box 19)
  - Bound volume: Reprints of the Section on Enzymes and Metabolism, National Institute of Arthritis and Metabolic Diseases, NIH, 1948-52 (Box 19)
  - Binder: slides of text, graphs, charts, and specimens 1973-75 and undated (Box 19)
  - Biochemistry 294, Winter 1992 (Box 20)
  - Department 1990 [folder with minutes, memos, financial statements, etc.] (Box 20)
  - Table 2 Students trained by each faculty member [covers training period of the 1960s-1980s] (Box 20)
  - Germ Stories [poems] (Box 20)
  - Slides of text, graphs, charts, and specimens-5 binders and one stack (Box 20)
  - Tube containing award certificate from city of Osaka, Japan (with English translation) 2004 (Box 20)
  - Reprints (Box 21)
  - Reprints (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 26)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 27)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, chronological (Box 30)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2002-186
  - Correspondence file re book DNA Sequencing, 1973-76 (Box 1)
  - Letters of recommendation, 1980-88 (Box 1)
  - Trip files, 1996, 1997 Jan.-Mar (Box 1)
  - Notes of graduate student James Flynn on biochemistry, mathematics and physics (Box 1)
  - Trip files, Apr.-Dec. 1997 (Box 2)
  - Annual Review Article, 10/22/1998 (Box 2)
  - File re several publications, 1997-98 (Box 2)
  - Transcript of UC-Berkeley oral history with Kornberg (1997) (Box 2)
  - Transcripts from Du Pont trial (Du Pont v Cetus regarding patents) 1989-91, v. 1-4 (Box 2)
  - Transcripts from Du Pont trial 1991, v. 5-17 (Box 3)
  - Additional materials re Du Pont trial, 1989-81 (correspondence, copies of articles, etc.) (Box 3)
  - Transcripts from Du Pont trial 1991, v. 18-21 (Box 4)
  - Other transcripts/documents from trial 1990 (Box 4)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," typescript (Box 4)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," correspondence, 1989-93 (Box 4)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," letters and reviews, 1989-91 (Box 4)
  - Khorana, Dr. H. Gobind – correspondence, 1955-68 (Box 4)
  - Medical school 1938: biochemistry class notes (Box 4)
  - "A Kennedy Plan" 12/7/60 [one page re development in Latin America of medical research institutes] (Box 4)
  - Photograph and neg of Kornberg portrait (Box 4)
  - DNA polymerase mechanism – notes, illustrations, correspondence, articles, 1969-71 (Box 4)
  - DNA duplication, DNA polymerase – assorted articles, clippings, 1954-73 (Box 4)
  - DNA duplication, DNA polymerase – correspondence, notes, charts, 1955-72 (Box 4)
  - Washington University, Dept of Microbiology – exams and miscellany, 1958-60 (Box 4)
  - Szilard, Leo, – letter and petition in response to invasion of Cuba, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Sherberg, Esther, letter, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Kornberg – discharge from U.S. Public Health Service, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Kornberg – press release and c.v., 1959 (Box 4)
  - Weizmann Institute – Bay Area (Box 5)
  - Weizmann Institute (Box 5)
  - Stanford Correspondence, 1973-86 (Box 5)
  - DNA Replication – update 1981 (correspondence) (Box 5)
  - Book – permissions (Box 5)
  - DNA Replication – requests for figure permission (Box 5)
  - DNA Replication – figure permissions (Box 5)
  - Book – DNA Replication (Box 5)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," preliminary work, interviews, comments and communications (Box 5)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," draft (Box 5)
  - "For the Love of Enzymes," image (color transparency) (Box 5)
  - Berk Foundation Awards Dinners, programs (Box 5)
  - Kornberg's diaries (calendars), 1966/67-2001 (Box 5)
  - Figure plates for DNA Replication and other publications (Box 6)
  - Assorted publications, mostly biographical re Kornberg (Box 7)
  - "Scientists' Lounge" with A. Kornberg and Dr. Osamm Hayaishi; unlabelled, 1971 Apr 12; 2 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 7)
  - Certificates, programs, calendars featuring Kornberg, galleys of For the Love of Enzymes, and two plaques (Box 8)
  - Plaques and framed items (Box 9)
  - Posters
    - 1. Hearts and Minds The Life and Science of Alejandro Zaffaroni (Box MC)
    - 2. "Mechanisms of E. Coli DNA Replication" – Basic Sciences Research Coloquia – Stanford University School of Medicine, Oct. 20, 1983 (Box MC)
    - 3. Buzz Baldwin Symposium, Berkeley, July 30, 1998 (Box MC)
    - 4. Book jacket (2 copies) for Kornberg's For the Love of Enzymes (Box MC)
    - 5. Vedua di S. Gimignano [old map reproduction] signed by 21 people "To Arthur Kornberg with affection" (Box MC)
    - 6. Gene Action – '95 In Appreciation of Charley [Yanofsky], Asilomar, April 1995. (2 copies plus letter and list of attendees) (Box MC)
    - 7. I. Robert Lehman Symposium Seventieth Year 1994 (Box MC)
    - 8. The Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine 1995. Edward B. Lewis, Christine Nusslein-Volhard, Eric F. Wieschaus. (Box MC)
    - 9. 1979 Silliman Memorial Lectures by Arthur Kornberg (Box MC)
- Profiles in Science images and metadata, 2007 Sep 14; Accession ARCH-2007-322; 400 megabyte(s); (321 computer files in 4 directories)
  As part of its Profiles in Science project, the National Library of Medicine has collaborated with Stanford University Libraries Department of Special Collections and University Archives to digitize and make available over the World Wide Web a selection of the Arthur Kornberg Papers for use by educators and researchers. This site provides access to the portions of the Arthur Kornberg Papers of Stanford University Libraries Department of Special Collections and University Archives that have been selected for digitization. Individuals interested in conducting research in the Arthur Kornberg Papers are invited to contact Stanford University Libraries Department of Special Collections and University Archives.
  - [Notes on bile pigments], 6/7/1939; WHBBBB; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    For several years in medical school, Kornberg developed an interest in bile pigments and benign jaundice, and conducted a small study on the incidence of Gilbert's disease among medical students. The resulting publication would lead to a research job at the National Institutes of Health in 1942.; Item is handwritten.
  - Draft memorandum from Arthur Kornberg to Floyd S. Daft regarding fellowship questionnaires, circa 1948; WHBBBC; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    This memo to his NIH section chief, Floyd Daft, detailed Kornberg's criteria for awarding postdoctoral fellowships.; Item is handwritten.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Fritz Lipmann, 5/12/1949; WHBBBD; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to biochemist Fritz Lipmann, Kornberg provided details about the enzyme he had purified for splitting DPN (diphosphopyridine nucleotide).
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Alan Mehler, 2/21/1949; WHBBBF; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    This letter to his friend Alan Mehler discussed the difficulties involved in Kornberg's ongoing studies of metabolic enzymes, and also mentioned the visit of the eminent German biochemist Otto Warburg.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Edwin G. Kreb, 2/17/1949; WHBBBG; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to his friend and prospective colleague Edwin Kreb, Kornberg described the benefits of working at NIH, as well as his feelings about the changes that were occurring there at the time, such as the building of the new Clinical Center.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Severo Ochoa, 1/24/1949; WHBBBH; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to his former mentor Severo Ochoa, Kornberg discussed the various challenges involved with using different yeast cultures as sources for enzymes.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Severo Ochoa, 12/31/1948; WHBBBJ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to his former mentor Severo Ochoa, Kornberg asked if Ochoa could return some Zwischenferment (the enzyme glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase) Kornberg had sent him, as the most recent batch wasn't proving as useful for their current experiments. He also reported feeling rather discouraged with the slow progress of his work on metabolic coenzymes.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Kenneth E. Holt, 12/23/1948; WHBBBK; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Kornberg and other enzymologists were aided in their work by researchers at the Anheuser-Busch brewery, who provided supplies of "cleaned" yeast for use as enzyme sources, as illustrated by this letter.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to J. Oliver Lampen, 10/15/1948; WHBBBL; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Biologists and biochemists during the 1940s and 1950s frequently shared their supplies of enzymes and other products of their labs, as there was often no other source. In this letter to J. O. Lampen, a friend from his time at the Cori lab, Kornberg regretted that he had no ready supplies of nicotinamide derivatives to send, and also discussed his current experiments.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Carl F. Cori, 10/6/1948; WHBBBM; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to his former mentor Carl Cori, Kornberg described his recent success with a new enzyme, and some insights about the role of inorganic pyrophosphate in metabolic processes, and asked Cori to review the report he was preparing on this work.
  - Letter from G. A. LePage to Arthur Kornberg, 11/30/1949; WHBBBN; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Kornberg had earlier requested information from G. A. LePage about his new method for preparing TPN (triphosphopyridine nucleotide), but the product he made using the method was not satisfactory. In this letter, LePage discussed possible reasons for Kornberg's problems with the process.
  - Letter from G. A. LePage to Arthur Kornberg, 5/10/1949; WHBBBP; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Interested in using TPN (triphosphopyridine nucleotide) for his next series of enzyme studies, Kornberg had written to G. A. LePage for information about his new method for preparing TPN. In this response, LePage detailed the equipment and supplies Kornberg's lab would need to make TPN.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Alex B. Novikoff, 5/23/1951; WHBBBS; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter, Kornberg responded to Novikoff's request for information about preparation of Zwischenferment (the enzyme glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase) and samples to begin the process.
  - Letter from Alex B. Novikoff to Arthur Kornberg, 5/8/1951; WHBBBT; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter, biochemist Alex Novikoff asked Kornberg for information about preparing Zwischenferment (the enzyme glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase) and several other substances needed for the process.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Herman M. Kalckar, 3/21/1951; WHBBBV; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to biochemist Herman Kalckar, Kornberg provided him with information about the NIH research grants process, and also gave him an update on his work on nucleotide synthesis.
  - Letter from Carl F. Cori to Arthur Kornberg, 2/15/1951; WHBBBX; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Kornberg's former mentor Carl Cori wrote to suggest another possible interpretation of a reaction involving TPN, and added a postscript saying, "What mysterious creatures enzymes are."
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Henry A. Lardy, 2/6/1951; WHBBBY; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to biochemist Henry Lardy, Kornberg shared his recent work on the pathway of uridine triphosphate synthesis, part of the early work that led him to nucleotide synthesis, and ultimately to DNA synthesis.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to W. E. Cohn, 1/17/1951; WHBBBZ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter, Kornberg congratulated biochemist Waldo Cohn on his recent success in isolating single nucleotides from RNA, and discussed his own recent work (closely related to Cohn's) with the nucleotide pyrophosphatase derived from potatoes.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Robert K. Morton, 11/16/1961; WHBBCC; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Robert Morton, an Australian biochemist, had recently found that baker's yeast contained a cytochrome (a protein involved in electron transfer in cell metabolism) with a DNA component. That DNA proved to have different base ratios than the yeast's nuclear DNA. He had suggested that this DNA could be used in understanding nucleotide sequences, and Kornberg had been working with some samples Morton sent, looking at their ability to prime DNA synthesis with his polymerase. In this letter, he reported some of his findings to Morton.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to W. E. Cohn, 2/24/1950; WHBBCD; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Biologists and biochemists during the 1940s and 1950s frequently shared their supplies of enzymes and other products of their labs, as there was often no other source. In this letter to Waldo Cohn, Kornberg apologized for the quality of a previous sample sent, and provided more specific information about its requirements.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Carl F. and Gerty Cori, 9/28/1950; WHBBCF; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter to his former mentors, Carl and Gerty Cori, Kornberg thanked them for good wishes regarding his Paul-Lewis Award, and told them of his ongoing lab work, changes at NIH, and the arrival of his third son, Kenneth.
  - Letter from G. David Novelli to Arthur Kornberg, 11/6/1950; WHBBCG; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Biologists and biochemists during the 1940s and 1950s frequently shared their supplies of enzymes and other products of their labs, as there was often no other source. In this letter, biochemist G. David Novelli reported to Kornberg on his experiments with a sample of Kornberg's nucleotide-splitting enzyme.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to G. David Novelli, 11/14/1950; WHBBCH; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    In this letter, Kornberg responded to biochemist G. David Novelli's letter describing the activity of an enzyme Kornberg had sent him.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to the editors of the Journal of Biological Chemistry, 1/29/1958; WHBBCK; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to John T. Edsall, 12/11/1957; WHBBCL; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to the editors of the Journal of Biological Chemistry, 12/11/1957; WHBBCM; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from John T. Edsall to Arthur Kornberg, 12/27/1957; WHBBCN; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Paul Berg to Arthur Kornberg, 7/14/1970; WHBBCP; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Leslie E. Orgel to Arthur Kornberg, circa Aug 1969; WHBBCQ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Includes a note from Francis Crick.; Item is handwritten.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Leslie E. Orgel and Francis Crick, 8/19/1969; WHBBCR; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Julius Marmur to Arthur Kornberg, 1/28/1960; WHBBCT; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from I. Robert Lehman to Julius Marmur, 2/9/1960; WHBBCV; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from H. George Mandel to Arthur Kornberg, 1/7/1960; WHBBCW; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to H. George Mandel, 1/11/1960; WHBBCX; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Andre Lwoff, 10/6/1960; WHBBCZ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to James O. Eastland, 10/7/1960; WHBBDB; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Van R. Potter, 7/5/1960; WHBBDD; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Robert L. Sinsheimer to Arthur Kornberg, 10/6/1960; WHBBDF; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from William F. Dove to Arthur Kornberg, 9/30/1971; WHBBDG; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to William F. Dove, 10/15/1971; WHBBDH; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from William F. Dove to Arthur Kornberg, 10/18/1971; WHBBDJ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Bruce Alberts to Arthur Kornberg, 3/23/1971; WHBBDK; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Bruce Alberts, 8/6/1971; WHBBDL; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Paul Englund, 12/17/1971; WHBBDM; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Senator Edward M. Kennedy, 3/27/1978; WHBBDN; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Item is a photocopy.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Paul N. McCloskey, Jr, 8/8/1977; WHBBDX; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Donald S. Fredrickson, 2/25/1977; WHBBDY; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Henry S. Kaplan, 7/16/1957; WHBBFB; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Robert H. Alway, 6/18/1957; WHBBFD; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Robert H. Alway to Arthur Kornberg, 6/13/1957; WHBBFF; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Henry S. Kaplan to Arthur Kornberg, 6/24/1957; WHBBFG; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Henry S. Kaplan, 1/6/1958; WHBBFH; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Alexander Rich, 3/14/1957; WHBBFK; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Howard K. Schachman, 11/15/1956; WHBBFL; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Robert L. Sinsheimer, 12/14/1956; WHBBFM; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Maurice H. F. Wilkins to Arthur Kornberg, 8/20/1956; WHBBFN; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Item is handwritten.
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Maurice H. F. Wilkins, 10/11/1956; WHBBFP; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Leon A. Heppel, 3/9/1955; WHBBFQ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to John R. Van Wazar, 11/4/1955; WHBBFR; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to H. Gobind Khorana, 1/10/1956; WHBBFS; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Robert H. Alway to Arthur Kornberg, 7/1/1957; WHBBFT; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Frederick E. Terman, 2/6/1958; WHBBFV; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - [Telegram invitation to a White House meeting with Lyndon Johnson], 9/30/1964; WHBBGB; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to James A. Shannon, 3/11/1968; WHBBGC; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Robert Baldwin to Arthur Kornberg, 5/20/1959; WHBBGD; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Robert Baldwin, 5/27/1959; WHBBGF; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - [Biochemistry 101 exam], 1960-1961; WHBBGG; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - [Biochemistry 101 exam], 1961-1962; WHBBGH; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to H. Gobind Khorana, 2/28/1957; WHBBGJ; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to H. Gobind Khorana, 3/8/1957; WHBBGK; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from H. Gobind Khorana to Arthur Kornberg, 3/18/1957; WHBBGL; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Letter from Arthur Kornberg to Robert K. Morton, 10/29/1962; WHBBGP; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
    Robert Morton, an Australian biochemist, had recently found that baker's yeast contained a cytochrome (a protein involved in electron transfer in cell metabolism) with a DNA component. That DNA proved to have different base ratios than the yeast's nuclear DNA. He had suggested that this DNA could be used in understanding nucleotide sequences, and Kornberg had been working with some samples Morton sent, looking at their ability to prime DNA synthesis with his polymerase. In this letter, Kornberg apologized for letting other projects delay his work on the Morton DNA.
  - Letter from Muriel Beadle to Arthur Kornberg, 1/26/1965; WHBBGR; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)